Man, this is weird.
이거 엽기다
크런치 선장의 눈썹이
모자에 달린 거 알았어?
Ever realize Cap'n Crunch's
eyebrows are on his hat?
That's what's weird?
웬 엽기? 그래 봬도
40년 간 시리얼의 선장이라고
The man's been captain
of a cereal for 40 years.
왜?
What?
The spoon!
You licked and you put.
숟가락 말이야
입에 넣었다가 그냥 넣어?
네가 방금 그랬어
You licked and you put.
Yeah, so?
그게 뭐?
Don't you see how gross that is?
It's like you using my toothbrush!
더러운 짓이란 거 몰라?
칫솔을 같이 쓰는 거나 같아
내 칫솔 썼어?
You used my toothbrush?
배수구 막혔을 때
빨간 칫솔을 쓸 뿐이야
Only because I used the red one
to unclog the drain.
Mine is the red one!
빨간 건 내 칫솔이야!
깡통을 따 놔서 온통
벌레를 끓게 하지를 않나
Oh, God!
Can open. Worms everywhere!
Why can't we use the same toothbrush...
비누는 같이 쓰면서
칫솔은 왜 안 돼?
... but we can use the same soap?
Because soap is soap.
It's self-cleaning.
비누는 비누니까!
자체 세척력이 있잖아
The next time you shower...
좋아, 그럼 샤워할 때
...think about the last thing I wash
and the first thing you wash.
내가 발 닦은 비누로
네가 얼굴 씻는다는 걸 생각해
The One Where Joey Moves Out
- 안녕
Look at you fancy lads!
기분들이 좋구나?
What's the occasion?
무슨 일이야?
You know that guy on my show
that's in a coma?
내 드라마에서
혼수상태였던 애 알지?
He's having a brunch.
걔가 좀 나아졌어
Ready when you are.
- 준비됐으면 가자
- 그래
I can't believe you're
actually getting tattoos.
어떻게 문신할 생각을 다했어?
You guys are getting tattoos?
- 뭐? 문신을 한다구?
- 그래
But you cannot tell Ross
because I wanna surprise him.
로스한테는 비밀이다
놀라게 해줄 거야
Wow, this is wild!
What are you gonna get?
참 야성적이다
뭘 새길 건데?
I'm getting a lily.
난 백합을 새길래
For my mom, because her name's Lily.
우리 엄마 이름이 백합이거든
That's lucky. What if
her name was Big Ugly Splotch?
다행이다
할미꽃이었으면 어쩔 뻔했냐?
-Where you getting it?
-On my shoulder.
- 어디에다 할 건데?
- 어깨에
What?
어깨에 뭐가 있는데?
What's on your shoulder?
새
A chip.
-A tattoo. I'm getting a tattoo.
-A tattoo?
문신을 하려고 해
문신? 그런 걸 왜 하려고?
Why? Why would you wanna do that?
- 안녕?
You don't think
they're kind of cool?
멋있는 생각 아냐?
No. Sorry, I don't.
아니, 평생 남을 흉터에
왜 돈을 들이는지 몰라
Why would anyone pay someone
to scar their body for life?
그러다 잘못되면 어떡해?
What if it doesn't come out right?
자를 때마다 맘에 안 드는
머리를 갖는 꼴이지
It's like having
a bad haircut all the time.
Why is everyone staring at me?
왜 날 쳐다봐?
Sign this card for Dad.
Richard will be here soon.
아빠 생일카드에 한마디 써
곧 리차드가 올 거야
Richard's going to the party too?
리차드도 함께 가?
He's my parents' best friend.
He has to go.
부모님의 친구시니까
당연히 가야지
So is today the day
you'll tell them about you two?
그럼 오늘 둘의 관계를
밝힐 거야?
Yeah, for my dad's birthday,
I decided to give him a stroke.
그래, 생신선물로
뇌졸중을 선사할까 봐
그건 당연히 말씀드려야 해
No, I think you should tell them.
안 돼, 아직 리차드의 감정을
확실히 알지도 못하는걸
I don't know how serious he is.
Until I do, I won't say anything.
I don't think
Mom and Dad would mind.
엄마 아빠는 신경 안 쓰실 거야
Remember when you were 9
and Richard was 30, Dad said...
네가 9살, 리차드가 서른일 때
아빠가 그러셨지
... "God, I hope they get together."
'둘이 친해 보라고'
Shall we?
- 들어가자
- 잠깐, 서 봐
Okay, wait.
You know what?
자리를 바꿔
오빠가 가운데에 서
Ross, let's switch places.
You get in the middle.
This looks like we're trying
to cover something up.
뭔가 숨긴다는 낌새가
풍기면 어떡하지?
리차드에게 안겨서 들어가도
전혀 눈치 못 채실 거야
You could come in straddling him,
they still wouldn't believe it.
- 저희들 왔어요
- 왔구나, 내 아기들!
We're here!
-Hi, kids!
-The children!
-Happy birthday, Dad.
-Thank you.
- 생신 축하드려요, 아빠
- 고맙다
- 잘지내셨어요, 엄마?
- 축하하네
Happy birthday!
So you kids thanked
Dr. Burke for the ride?
버크 박사님께
태워 줘서 고맙다고 했니?
Actually, Mom, I think Monica
thanked him for the both of us.
모니카가 제 몫까지
고맙다고 했을 거예요
기차를 타고 왔니?
So you kids take the train in?
No, Richard Burke gave them a ride.
리차드가 태워 줬대요
Speaking of whom...
저이가 시내에서 스무 살짜리
얼빠진 애랑 돌아다니더래
... I hear he's got some
20-year-old twinkie in the city.
Finger cramp! Oh, God!
손가락에 쥐가 났어요
죄송해요
Sorry. Here, let me get that, Mom.
제가 닦을게요, 엄마
그래서 리차드가
아가씨 코너에서 쇼핑했군
So Richard's shopping
in the junior section?
Are we still on that?
아직도 그 얘기예요?
그 여자애 머리가
의심스럽다니까
You just know she's got
the lQ of a napkin.
분명 얼굴도 아닐 거야
She's probably not even pretty.
Just young enough so that
everything is still pointing up.
새파랗게 젊어서
탱탱한 것 말고 볼 게 있겠어?
Can you believe this place?
- 어마어마하지?
- 그래, 멋진 아파트다
I know. This is a great apartment.
In the bathroom there's mirrors
on both sides of you.
화장실에 갔더니
거울이 양쪽에 있더라
When you're in there, it's like
peeing with the Rockettes.
거기서 오줌을 누면
로켓 발사 같을 거야
Well, there's my fantasy come true.
네 꿈이 실현되겠구나
Seriously.
진짜야
- 잘 왔어
- 이봐, 정말 좋은 아파트야
We were just saying, great apartment!
Thanks. You want it?
고마워, 너 살래?
난 더 큰 데로 이사가니까
네가 이 집을 사
I'm moving to a bigger place.
You should take this one.
Can you see me in a place like this?
- 나보고 이런 집에서 살라고?
- 왜 안 돼?
Why not? You hate park views
and high ceilings?
바깥 풍경이 맘에 안 들어?
Come on, I'll show you the kitchen.
부엌을 보여 줄게, 이리 와
That's all right,
I saw a kitchen this morning.
괜찮아, 친구
난 아침에 보고 왔어
On TV.
TV로 말야
'입다물어', '알았어'
Stop talking. Okay!
-Come on, tell us!
-ls she really 20?
- 어서 말해 봐
- 정말 스무 살이야?
I am not telling you guys anything.
자네들한텐 말해 봤자야
이 사람아, 내 생일이잖나
대리만족이라도 해보자고
Come on, it's my birthday.
Let me live vicariously!
Dad, you really don't want to do that.
아빠, 진심은 아니시겠죠?
What's a little midlife crisis
between friends?
중년의 친구들끼리
말 못할 게 뭐 있겠나?
그만 좀 해
Would you let it go?
그 기분 이해해, 쉰 살에
내가 포르쉐를 장만한 반면
I know what you're going through.
When I turned 50, I got the Porsche.
자네는 고속열차를
꼬신 셈이지
You got your own little speedster.
제발, 그런 게 아니라고
-Seriously, it's not like that.
-Tell you what.
이러면 어때? 주말에
내 포르쉐를 빌려 줄 테니까...
Maybe one of these weekends
you can borrow the car and I could
제발 더 이상 말하지 마세요
Dad, I beg you not
to finish that sentence!
What? I'm kidding!
농담이다, 내가 미쳤니?
포르쉐를 발려 주게
You know I'd never let him
touch the Porsche.
Okay, Rach.
어서 와, 레이첼
어떤 백합이 좋아?
Which lily?
This lily or that lily?
이거, 아님 저거?
-Well, l
-I like this lily.
난 이게 맘에 들어
It's more open
and that's like my mom.
활짝 폈잖아
우리 엄마처럼 개방적이야
She had a more open, giving spirit.
무적의 싸움닭이다!
Foghorn Leghorn!
Blonde girl?
You're in room two.
거기 금발 아가씨!
2번 방으로 가요
Not-so-blonde girl, you're with me.
반만 금발인 아가씨는
날 따라와요
Here we go!
가자
You're not going.
안 가?
로스가 한 말 때문에 그래?
Is this because of what Ross said?
아냐
-Well, yeah, maybe.
-I don't believe this.
아니, 어쩌면...
기가 막혀, 어떻게 그렇게 사귀니?
로스가 네 주인이라도 돼?
Is this how this relationship works?
Ross equals boss?
아님 뭐야?
지금이 1922년이니?
Come on, what is this, 1922?
What's 1922?
1922년에 무슨 일이 있었는데?
Just, you know, a long time ago.
아주 옛날이란 거지
남자가 모든 걸
간섭하던 때였잖아
When men used to tell women
what to do a lot.
이후에 참정권이 생겼지만
난 그것도 맘에 안 들어!
Then there was suffrage, which was
a good thing. But it sounds horrible.
Do you want this tattoo?
문신을 하고 싶긴 한 거야?
Yes, I do.
It's just that Ross
그럼, 난 로스가...
얘!
로스가 네 주인 맞지?
Is your boyfriend the boss of you?
- 아냐
- 그럼 누가 주인이야?
Who is the boss of you?
You?
너?
아니, 바로 너야
You are the boss of you!
당당히 걸어 들어가서
엉덩이에 하트 문신을 넣어!
You march in there and
get that tattoo on your hip!
Go!
어서!
How you doing?
- 어때?
- 저더러 얼빠졌대요
I'm a twinkie!
Really? I'm a hero.
그래? 난 영웅 됐는데
This is so hard.
너무 힘들어요
Yeah, I know. I hate it too.
나도 이러는 거 싫어
그냥 말해 버리자
Look, maybe we should just tell them.
Maybe we should just tell
your parents first.
당신 부모님께 먼저요
My parents are dead.
모두 돌아가셨어
God, you are so lucky!
당신은 정말 행운아예요!
- 오해하지 말아요
- 견뎌 보자고
I mean
Well, you know what I mean.
다 잘될 거야
Just hang in there, okay?
Okay, I'll go out first, all right?
- 먼저 나갈게
- 알았어요
Judy! Going to the bathroom.
Good for you!
쥬디, 화장실에 가려고?
잘됐어!
Thank you, Richard.
I appreciate the support.
고마워요, 리차드
응원해 줘서요
여보
Honey.
Seen my Harmon Kille brew bat?
Bob doesn't believe I have one.
내 야구방망이 못 봤어?
밥 좀 보여 주게
I have no idea.
나도 몰라요
Did you know Richard
has a twinkie in the city?
리차드한테 얼빠진 애가
있다는 거 들었어요?
딴사람이 됐다니까
완전히 꽃피는 봄날이야
I know. He's a new man.
It's like a scene from Cocoon.
I just never would have
pictured Richard with a bimbo.
리차드가 그렇고 그런 애랑
놀아난다니 상상이 안 돼요
일전에 조니 샤피노에 대해
얘기하던데
He told Johnny Shapiro
that she's quite a girl.
He told Johnny that he thinks
he's falling in love with her.
그 애랑 사랑에 빠졌나 봐
그래요?
-Really?
-I've never seen him this happy.
그렇게 행복해 하는 건 첨 봐
So, Jack...
여보, 당신 같으면 날
젊은 여자와 바꾸겠어요?
...ever think about trading me in
for a younger model?
말도 안 되지
Of course not.
With you, it's like
I've got two 25-year-olds.
당신은 25살짜리
두 명 분은 돼
Oh, Jack, stop!
- 이러지 말아요!
- 봐줘
Come on!
It's my birthday!
오늘은 내 생일이잖아
Can we drop this?
그만 하자, 그 녀석
아파트에 난 관심 없어
I am not interested
in the guy's apartment.
Oh, please. I saw the way
you were checking out his moldings.
그 조형물을 뚫어지게
볼 때는 언제고?
You want it.
넌 그걸 원해
Why would I want another apartment?
내가 왜 다른 아파트를 원해?
I've already got
an apartment that I love.
내가 좋아하는 집은 여기야!
It wouldn't kill you
to say it once in a while.
평소에 그런 말하면
어디 덧나냐?
All right. You want the truth?
I'm thinking about it.
좋아, 사실대로 말할까?
진작부터 고려하고 있었어
-What?
-I'm sorry.
- 뭐야?
- 미안해
28살이 될 때까지
혼자 산 적이 없어
I'm 28. I've never lived alone...
...and I'm at a place
where I got enough money...
이제 그 집을 살 만큼
돈도 있고 룸메이트도 필요 없어
...that I don't need a roommate.
I don't need a roommate either.
필요 없기는 나도 마찬가지야
혼자서도 집을 꾸릴 수 있다고
I can afford to live here by myself.
은 숟가락을 핥아 줄 친구는
일주일에 한 번만 부르면 돼!
I may have to bring in somebody
once a week to lick the silverware.
Why are you getting
so bent out of shape?
왜 점점 비뚤어져 가냐?
We didn't agree to live
together forever.
너랑 영원히 살 순 없어
우린 영원한 짝꿍이 아니라구
We're not Bert and Ernie.
You know what?
그거 알아?
If this is the way you feel...
그런 식으로 느낀다면
네 맘대로 해
...then maybe you should take it.
-That's how I feel.
-Then maybe you should take it!
- 그래, 그렇게 느꼈다
- 그럼 맘대로 해
Maybe I will!
- 그래, 그럴 거야
- 잘된 일이야
-Fine with me!
-Great!
좋아, 네 진짜 친구랑
지내게 돼서 좋겠다
You can spend more quality time
with your real friends...
...the spoons!
숟가락 말야!
Whose drink can I freshen?
누구 잔 비운 사람?
디저트 먹을 시간이네?
Almost time for cake!
모니카, 괜찮아?
Mon, are you okay?
You remember that video
I found of Mom and Dad?
일전에 내가 찾은
엄마 아빠의 비디오 기억나?
- 응
- 방금 노컷 생중계로 봤어
Well, I just caught the live show.
- 나 좀 봐요
- 왜?
-Hey, there.
-What?
Nothing. I just heard
something nice about you.
그냥요, 당신에 관한
얘기를 들었어요
Really?
그래?
리차드!
당신 아들 애인 없죠?
-Your son isn't seeing anyone, is he?
-Not that I know of.
내가 알기로는 없어
I was thinking, why doesn't
he give Monica a call?
우리 모니카한테
전화하라고 하지 그래요?
그것 참... 생각이네
That's an idea.
Well, actually,
I'm already seeing someone.
실은 저 애인 있어요
Oh?
She never tells us anything.
얜 귀뜸도 안 해주지 뭐예요
로스, 넌 알고 있었니?
Ross, did you know
Monica's seeing someone?
엄마, 세상에 사람이
얼마나 많아요?
Mom, there are
so many people in my life.
Some are seeing people
and some aren't.
그러니 애인 있는 사람도
없는 사람도 있겠죠
Is that crystal?
이거 크리스털이에요?
So who's the mystery man?
수수께끼의 인물이 누구니?
Well, he's a doctor.
- 박사예요
- 진짜 박사?
A real doctor?
No, a doctor of meat.
아뇨, 빨래 박사요
Of course he's a real doctor.
당연히 진짜 박사죠
And he's handsome.
잘생기고 다정하고
엄마도 좋아하실 거예요
And he's sweet,
and I know you'd like him.
Well, that's wonderful.
그거 잘됐구나, 그럼...
Mom, it's okay.
맞아요, 엄마
It is, Judy.
그래, 쥬디
Jack!
여보?
Could you come in here for a moment?
잠깐 와 볼래요?
당장요
Now!
-Found it!
-I'll take that, Dad.
- 찾았어
- 제가 들고 있을게요
It seems your daughter and Richard
are something of an item.
당신 딸과 리차드가
심상치 않은 것 같아요
That's impossible.
He's got a twinkie in the city.
말도 안 돼
얼빠진 애는 어떡하구?
I'm the twinkie.
아빠, 제가 그 얼빠진 애예요
-You're the twinkie?
-She's not a twinkie!
- 네가 얼빠진 애라구?
- 절대 얼빠지지 않았네
Look, this is the best relationship
I've been in
제 말 들으세요
우린 이상적인 관계...
Oh, please! A relationship?
이런! 관계라구?
네, 관계요
Yes, a relationship!
For your information,
I'm crazy about this man.
전 이 사람한테 빠졌어요
Really?
정말이야?
그래요
내 생일 날 꼭
이런 얘길 들어야 해?
Am I supposed to stand here
and listen to this on my birthday?
아빠, 저한텐 잘된 일이에요
This is a good thing. You said
you've never seen Richard happier.
아빠도 리차드가
행복해 한다고 하셨잖아요
When did I say that?
내가 언제 그랬어?
Upstairs in the bathroom,
right before you felt up Mom!
위층 화장실에서
엄마를 만지기 전에요!
생일 축하합니다!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Jack
사랑하는 친구의
생일 축하합니다
Happy birthday to you
It looks so good!
Oh, I love it.
정말 예쁘다!
너무 맘에 들어
I know, so do l!
I'm so glad you made me do this.
나도 그래
이런 기회를 줘서 고마워
Okay, let me see yours.
너도 보여 줘
좋아, 네 것 다시 보자
Let's see yours again.
We just saw mine.
Let me see yours.
방금 봤잖아, 네 차례야
알았어
Oh, no!
이런...
It's gone! That's so weird.
사라졌어
이상하네, 어디로 갔을까?
I don't know how, where it went.
You didn't get it?
- 너 안 했니?
- 그래
Why not?
- 왜 안 했어?
- 미안해, 미안해
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
어떻게 이럴 수 있니?
하자고 조른 게 누군데
How could you do this to me?
This was your idea!
I know! I was gonna get it,
but he came in with this needle.
알아, 알아!
나도 할 생각이었는데
커다란 바늘을 가져오잖아
And did you know
they do this with needles?
바늘로 하는 줄 알고 있었니?
Really? You don't say?
그랬니? 내 건 고양이가
핥던 대바늘이었어!
Because mine was licked on by kittens!
- 안녕?
- 안녕
I'm sorry about what
- 아까는 미안했어
- 나도
-Yeah, me too.
-I know.
Do we need to hug?
이쯤에서 껴안아야...
그럴 거까지야...
No, we're all right.
So I got you something.
너한테 줄 게 있어
Plastic spoons!
일회용 숟가락이잖아!
-Great!
-Lick away, my man!
- 대단해
- 핥고 버려
These will go great in my new place
till I get real ones.
마침 잘됐다
새 집에서 써야지
What?
뭐?
I can't use these forever.
They're no friend of the environment.
이걸 평생 쓸 순 없잖아
환경도 생각해야지
No, I mean what's this
about your new place?
새 집이라니?
I'm moving out,
like we talked about.
나 이사가, 얘기했잖아
장난인 줄 알았는데
I didn't think that was serious.
You know, I thought
that was just a fight.
그냥 사소한 싸움이잖아
그래, 싸움이지
Well, it was a fight...
... based on serious stuff, remember?
뭐 때문에 싸웠느냐가 문제고
내 독립에 관한 거였잖아
About how I never
lived alone or anything?
I think it would be good for me.
Help me to grow...
이게 기회일 거야
홀로 성장할 기회... 어쨌거나
...or whatever.
그렇군
Well, there you go.
Hey, are you cool with this?
너 화났니? 난 이런 식으로
차갑게 헤어지긴 싫어
I don't wanna leave you high and dry.
나 뜨겁게 열받은 거 아냐
I've never been lower or wetter.
I'll be fine.
I'll just turn your...
난 괜찮아
... bedroom into a game room.
네 방에 오락 게임기나 두지 뭐
축구 게임대를 놓으면 되겠다
Put the foosball table in there.
Why do you get to keep the table?
왜 네가 가져?
I did pay for half of it.
내가 반을 보탰잖아
나머진 내가 냈어
I paid for the other half.
I'll tell you what.
I'll play you for it.
좋아, 이렇게 하자
내기 게임을 하는 거야
All right, you're on.
좋아, 너쯤이야
순식간에 무릎 꿇게 해주지
I can take two minutes
out of my day to kick your ass.
Your men will get scored on
more times than your sister.
네 누나하고나 해야
승리를 맛보시겠지
Which sister?
어느 누나 말야?
So are you sorry that I told them?
내가 부모님께 말해서
화났어요?
No. It's been a long time
since your dad and I went running.
그렇게 친한 사이도
아니었는데 뭐
Did you get it?
- 문신했니? 보자!
- 로스 여기 있어?
-ls Ross here?
-He went out for pizza.
- 아니, 피자 사러 갔어
- 그럼 빨리 봐
Okay, really quick.
That's great!
너무 예쁘다
Very tasteful.
고상한데
Wanna see mine? Wanna see mine?
- 내 것도 볼래?
- 그래
What? You didn't get one.
뭐? 하지도 않았잖아
Okay. Well then, what is this?
그럼 이건 뭐니?
What are we looking at?
뭘 보라는 거야?
That blue freckle?
그 파란 주근깨?
이게 제 문신이에요
That's my tattoo.
문신은 무슨
아무것도 아냐
That is not a tattoo.
That is a nothing.
I got her in the chair...
날 밀어부칠 땐 언제고
바늘도 안 댔는데 뛰쳐나갔지
...he barely touched her with the
needle, she screamed and that was it.
Okay, hi!
그래, 나야
이게 바로 내가
정말로 원하던 거였어
For your information,
this is exactly what I wanted.
This is a tattoo of the Earth as seen
from a great, great distance.
이건 아주 아주 먼 데서
내려다본 지구야
It's the way my mother
sees me from heaven.
하늘에 계신 우리 엄마가
내려다본 지구
Oh, what a load of crap!
웬 헛소리!
That is a dot!
그건 점이야
Your mother's in heaven going,
"Where the hell's my lily, you wuss!"
네 엄마가 하늘에서
'내 백합은 어디 있니?' 하시겠다
그건 문신이 아냐
이런 게 바로 문신이지!
That is not a tattoo!
This is a tattoo!
You got a tattoo?
문신했어?
Maybe.
아마...
But just a little one.
Phoebe got the whole world!
난 조그만 거야
피비는 지구를 문신했어
Well, let me see.
어디 보자
Well?
어때?
Well, it's really...
정말이지... 섹시하다
...sexy.
I wouldn't have thought
it would be, but...
이런 것일 줄은 몰랐어
...wow!
와...
Really?
- 정말?
- 응
So is it sore?
Or can you do stuff?
많아 아파?
지금 해도 괜찮을까?
I guess.
될 거야
Save us some pizza.
우리 피자 남겨 놔
Get it out of the corner!
구석에서 나와!
패스, 패스해!
Pass it! Pass it!
Stop talking to your men!
시끄러워 죽겠네
이겼다!
이젠 내 거지?
And the table is mine.
축하해
Congratulations.
너희들 놀러 올 거지?
You guys will still
come visit me, right?
Oh, yeah! You got the big TV.
그럼, 초대형 TV가 있는데
매일 가야지
We'll be over there all the time.
Except when we are here.
여기 있을 때는 빼고
I know you're just moving uptown,
but I'll really miss you.
가까운 데로 가는데
벌써 그리워지네
How can you not be
across the hall anymore?
맞아
문만 열면 있었는데
남은 음식은 누가 처리해 주며
전화는 누가 달아 주니?
Who's gonna eat all of our food
and tie up our phone lines
Is that my bra?
저거 내 브라야?
이걸로 뭐 했어?
-What are you doing with my bra?
-It's not what you think.
이상한 생각하지 마
지붕 너머로 물 풍선을 던졌어
We used it to fling
water balloons off the roof.
Remember? Those kids couldn't
even get theirs across the street.
기억나? 중학생들이 우리
구경하느라 길도 못 건넜잖아
Yeah, I remember.
그래, 기억나
Let's bring the rest of these
down to the truck.
짐들을 차로 나르자
고마워
축구 게임대는 가져갈 거야?
You want me to...
...give you a hand
with the foosball table?
아니, 너 가져
연습을 더 해야지
You keep it.
You need the practice.
Thanks.
고마워
이제 가야겠다
So...
... I guess this is it.
Yeah, right.
그래, 그래야지
I guess so.
다시 볼 수 있을까?
When am I gonna see you?
오늘 레이첼네 카페에서 보자
I'm guessing tonight
at the coffeehouse.
Right. Yeah. Okay.
그래, 그러자
Take care.
- 갈게
- 그래